It's been a while.
久しぶりです
It's still cute.
相変わらず可愛いですね
What have you been up to lately?
最近何してたんですか?
recently?
最近?
Did you do something on your day off?
休みの日とか何かしてたのかな?
I was playing.
遊んでました
What were you playing?
何して遊んでたの?
Lunch or something.
ランチとか
It's cute.
可愛いね
It's called lunch.
ランチって言うんだ
What kind of food do you like?
ご飯何好きなんですか?
I like gyoza.
餃子が好きです
Surprisingly?
意外に?
Are you a fan of lots of garlic?
ニンニクたっぷり派ですか?
I'm a generous person.
たっぷり派です
That's surprising.
意外ですね
I also like junk and bulky things.
ジャンク系の コッテリしたものも好きなんだ
I like it.
好きです
So you came again.
また来てくれたわけですね
People who like that kind of thing look up to it for power.
そういうのが好きな人っていうのは パワーに見上げてますから
I'm looking up to the power.
パワーに見上げてるんで
Hey, I've been too nervous to talk at all the other day, so I'm definitely not going to talk.
ちょっとね、この前は全然お話し的には 緊張しすぎて絶対もあ
I think I was embarrassed, and a lot of things happened.
って 恥ずかしかったのもあると思うし いろいろあってさ
You don't remember much, do you?
あんま覚えてないでしょ
Honesty.
正直
I think there was something like that, so I also asked a few questions.
っていうのがあったと思うので 僕もちょっとね 質問とかあんま
I couldn't do it.
でき なかったんですよ
So, is it okay if I talk to you briefly?
なので、ちょっと軽く お話しても平気かな?
What about the edge?
エッジはさ、 どうなのかな?
Do you like it?
好きなのかな?
I think you like it.
好きな方だと思います
That's right.
そう なんだ
Until now, do you remember the excited edge?
なんか今までさ、 で興奮したエッジとか覚えたりするかな?
Is it a little embarrassing?
ちょっと恥ずかしい?
Internet cafes.
ネットカフェとか
Ah, that's cute.
あ、かわいいね
Well, why are you excited?
それはさ、なんで興奮するの?
that...
あの...
Yeah yeah.
うんうん
There's no ceiling.
天井がない
A moonlit type.
月抜けタイプの
My voice came out.
声出ちゃった
I held back.
我慢した
Oh, I held back.
ああ、我慢したんだ
People might see it a little bit.
人にちょっと見られるかもしれない
I got excited because I thought I might be able to hear it.
聞こえるかもしれないっていうので 興奮したんだ
Like internet cafes.
ネットカフェとかね
I guess someone might see it after all.
ちょっとやっぱ誰か見られるかもしれないっていう
But this too, turn the camera.
でも これもさ、 カメラ回してさ、
Then, someone might see it.
それからさ、 誰かに見られるかもしれないじゃん
I'm watching it too.
俺も見てるしね
On the contrary, I might be more excited this week.
ちょっと逆に今週もっと興奮しちゃうかもね
surely.
確 かに
Do you do things like masturbate?
オナニーとかってさ、したりするのかな?
I will.
します
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Is that a hand?
それは手ですか?
Is it a phone call?
電話ですか?
Phone.
電話ね
Den Max?
電マックス?
Eh, where should I put the phone?
え、電話どこに当てるの?
chestnut.
栗
Can I try again?
もう一回いいですか?
It has ears.
耳あるんですよ
Apply to chestnuts.
栗に当てる
Glee?
グリー?
chestnut.
栗
That's a cute way to say it.
言い方かわいいね
Something like chestnuts.
栗とかって
You sound like a living thing.
生物みたいな言い方しますね
Yes, yes, yes.
はい はいはい
Is that what you're imagining?
それってさ、 想像してするの?
Or do you want to see something?
それとも何か見たりするの?
imagine?
想像?
Both already.
もうどっちも
When was the last time you had an onax?
最近いつ オナックスしたの?
About a week ago.
1週間前ぐらい
Well, you did quite a bit.
え、結構したんすね
Recently, I guess.
最近というかね
Yes, yes, yes.
はい はいはい
What did you imagine that to be like?
それはどういうのを想像したの?
It saw the video.
それは、映像を見た
What kind of video did you see?
どういうのを映像を見たの?
What genre?
どういうジャンル?
Hamedori or something.
はめどりとか
Is that so?
そうなんすか?
It was captured on camera, and I did something like that.
カメラに撮られたんですけど、 ちょっと あれしたんだ
That's right.
そうなんだ
So, do you want to replace it with yourself?
それはさ、自分に置き換えるの?
Or did you look at it objectively?
それとも、 客観視してみたの?
Objective view.
客観視
That's right.
そうなんだ
I wonder if there is someone like me?
私と同じ人がいるのかな?
It might look something like this.
みたい な感じになるかもしれないね
That's right.
そっかそっか
And then, today...
そしたらね、今日ね、
What kind of edge do you like? Or do you like flirting?
どう いう系のエッジが好きとか いちゃいちゃが好きとかさ、
I don't know what this is, but it's not abnormal.
ちょっとこう何だろう、 アブノーマルじゃないけどさ、
Only in situations like this, for example,
こういうところでしかさ、 例えばさ、
It's not SM, but like Sost SM, etc.
SMじゃないけどさ、ソーストSMとかさ、
Like, I like it when I get hit hard.
ちょっとこう、 激しめにやられた方が好きとかさ、
Is there such a thing?
そういうのがあったりするのかな?
But since I'm M, I like being attacked.
でもMだから、 攻められるのが好き
That's right.
そうなんだ
It's M.
Mなんだ
Why do I feel like I'm M?
なんでそう自分がMって感じたりするのかな?
Well, I like it now.
え、もう好きに
Oh, that's right, that's right.
ああ、そっかそっかそっか
But, I wonder if he doesn't have a boyfriend right now?
でもさ、なんかさ、 今彼さんいないのか、
Is it there or not?
いるのか、 い ないのかな?
When I did something, when I felt horny, etc.
した時とかさ、 ムラムラしたりとかした時とかさ、
Can I invite someone myself?
自分から誘ったりできるの?
Don't you do much?
あんましないの?
I might not be able to do that.
あんまできないかもしれない
I want you to notice it by touching it with your hands or something like that.
なんか 手でやたら触るとか、 そういう感じで 気づいてほしい
Does it feel like it?
感じ かな?
Just like you would do to your boyfriend, ask him to give you a pampering look.
彼氏にこうするような感じでさ、 甘える感じの顔やってもらって
Is it okay too?
も いいかな?
A sweet face?
甘える顔?
Like, I want to have sex.
えっちしたいな、みたいな
Can I just say I want to have sex?
えっちしたいなって言えばいい?
Is it like that?
そんな感じかな?
I wish I could create that kind of atmosphere.
そういう感じの雰囲気出してくれたら
I want to have sex.
えっちしたいな
I was totally blind, but it's embarrassing.
めちゃくちゃ盲目だったけど、 恥ずかしいよね
Well, it's coming now.
まあね、今ね、 来てますもんね
Mr. Diamond.
ダイヤさん
Mr. Shu Shudai.
シュシュダイさん
After all, it's not something I usually do,
やっぱさ、普段できないようなさ、
This too, someone might see it.
これもね、誰かに見られちゃうかもしれないよ
Me too, take pictures while watching.
僕もね、見ながら撮って
Maybe I'll join in.
もしかしたら俺は参加しちゃうかもしれない
Mr. Stahl, then Mr. Stahl, let's make some preparations.
シュタルさん、じゃあ、 シュタルさんちょっと準備したら、
I think I'll get ready, so could you wait a little while?
準備すると思うんで、 ちょっと待ってもらってもいいかな?
Actually, I'm already waiting.
実はもう待ってます
You can see it.
見えてきますよね
Can you see it?
見えてるかな?
Well, I know it's embarrassing, but please call me Dia-san.
じゃあ、恥ずかしいと思うけど、 ダイヤさんって呼んでもらって
Is that okay too?
も いいかな?
Mr. Diamond.
ダイヤさん
Oh, please.
あ、どうぞ
Hello.
こんにちは
Ah, I hope I don't have to run away so much.
あ、そんなに逃げなくてはいいですね
It's nice, the style is great.
いいっすね、スタイルいいっすね
Very stylish.
めっちゃスタイルいい
Ah, that's interesting.
あ、面白いしね
That's wonderful.
素晴らしいね
Oh, it's there, sexy.
あ、入ってる、セクシー
Is this there for you to touch?
これ、触ってもらうために入ってるんですか?
yes.
はい
To be touched?
触ってもらうために?
I see, it's amazing, it's a good mood.
なるほどね、すごい、ノリがいいんですね
Can I say it?
言われていい?
No, it's not really said.
いや、ほんまに言われない
With your body.
体で
I feel it.
感じます
I feel like I'm beautiful.
きれいって自覚があるんだね
beautiful.
き れい
You look beautiful today.
今日きれいだね
It's so beautiful, isn't it?
すごいきれいでしょ
It's smooth today.
今日すべすべだね
Creamy.
くりー
Do you know?
知ってるの?
Yeah.
うん
Oh, I told you so.
あ、言っちゃだね
Just tell me which one is better.
どこがいいのかちょっと言ってよ
Is there something you like about it?
好きなところが出てる?
Check it out?
調べてみ?
Check it out
調べてみて
please.
ください
Yes, yes, yes.
そう、 そう、そう
It was.
そうでした
I'm hungry now.
今、お腹が空いてる
I'm hungry.
お腹が空いてる
I'm hungry now.
今、お腹が空いてるよ